<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AAC</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="title_main">About</string>
    <string name="text1_about">
        OUR MISSION\n\nTo provide a forum to address issues affecting the Afghan-American community, and a platform to facilitate dialogue, collaborate, and build relationships to strengthen our diaspora. \n\nOUR VISION\n\nAn empowered, supportive, and engaged Afghan-American community.\n\nOUR REASON\n\nThe Afghan-American diaspora has historically lacked a safe space for candid discussions about the issues most pertinent to us. Traditionally, our community has come together almost exclusively in social settings, including weddings, concerts, picnics, and sports tournaments. However, none of these gatherings have been conducive to serious discussions about the state of our community. Too often, taboo topics have been swept under the proverbial Afghan rug, never to be broached or approached.\n\nGiven the impoverished state of Afghanistan, it is understandable that so much of our diaspora’s civic attention has focused on humanitarian relief for the Motherland. But in doing so, we have lost sight of our own community\’s struggles here in the United States. Almost every Afghan family landed in the U.S. as refugees with few resources, but many are still trapped in the same socioeconomic class. According to the “Bay Area Muslim Study” by Drs. Farid Senzai and Hatem Bazian, Afghans have the fewest households making over $100,000 among any Muslim group in the San Francisco Bay Area. We are also the least educated group, with less than half of our community having pursued higher education. The fact that we only have statistics on Bay Area Afghans, and only in relation to other Muslim ethnicities, speaks to our underrepresented status nationwide—and just how much work we have to do as a community to move forward.\n\nOUR CORE VALUES\n\n• Build a sense of community around a diverse Afghan-American identity, while learning and embracing Afghan culture and history. \n• Provide a space for networks built on professional and academic connections for guidance, career growth, and development of leadership skills.\n• Engage in critical dialogue around challenging issues and activate the change to find solutions in our community.\n• Internalize norms and values that demonstrate respect, accountability, and flexibility towards different perspectives.\n\nA WAY FORWARD\n\nThis is where the Afghan-American Conference comes into the picture. AAC provides a forum for our community to address these difficult topics in a respectful, forward-thinking manner. It is a grassroots effort at shedding light on these pressing issues, inspiring action, and activating change from within the community. We won’t be able to address everything, nor do we have the answers to almost anything. Let us get the conversation started, let us share resources, and let us find those solutions together as a community.\n\nOUR COMMITTMENT\n\nThe Afghan-American Conference commits to keeping our conference an inclusive and safe environment for all of our participants.\n\nIf you have any questions, please do not hesitate to contact us.\n\nDIVERSITY\n\nDiversity is essential to our work at AAC. We know our Motherland, and our diaspora, are both incredibly diverse, and that diversity itself enriches the experience of attendees and allows for the full rich tapestry of our community to be present and contributing to the conference and organization. We know that to truly succeed, our space should be representative of our diversity as a community. We know we may fall short, but our goal is to strive and aim higher.\n\n Learn More: https://tinyurl.com/y5eh8w9s\n\nMENTAL WELLNESS\n\nOne of the recurring themes that arise during the weekend of our conference is mental health. The importance of mental health is often threaded through our keynotes, S.E.E.D. Talks, sessions, and panels. \n\nAs our community bands together to move forward, one stigmatized yet present challenge is maintaining mental wellness both for our loved ones and us.\n\nLearn More: https://tinyurl.com/y5tz9uqs\n\nANTI-DISCRIMINATION &amp; HARASSMENT\n\nOur policy was established to address issues, including harassment, abuse, and discrimination,  that have taken place within AAC.  It provides a way for AAC to address these situations and uphold a safe, supportive, empowered, and engaged community. It applies to all members of the conference and individuals that attend an AAC event or engage in conversations on AAC’s virtual platforms.  We are currently finalizing a revised and more comprehensive Code of Conduct policy that will be released shortly.\n\nLearn More: https://tinyurl.com/yxgyrv6w\n\nTHE CONFERENCE\n\nThe Afghan-American Conference is an annual nationwide conference for young community leaders to engage in meaningful dialogue, grow professionally and build relationships.\n\nThe conference is equal parts professional, cultural, spiritual, social, and personal. It is a holistic event consisting of keynote speeches, professional panels, skill-building workshops, roundtable discussions, safe space caucuses, town halls, networking mixers, entertainment, and even TED-style Talks.\n\nRead testimonials from past participants: https://tinyurl.com/y34tljar\n\nTHE EVOLUTION \n\nIn April 2015, the first Afghan-American Conference was hosted at U.C. Berkeley by eight young Afghan-Americans from across the United States. The space was an opportunity for our diaspora to have difficult conversations in an engaging and respectful way. Since then, the conference has grown and spread across the nation.\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="title_planning_team"> </string>
    <string name="text1_planning_team">
        The Afghan-American Conference started as an idea implemented by a group of students and working professionals volunteering remotely from across the United States. Our team is comprised of individuals with deep passion for our community, a commitment to service, and diverse personal and professional experiences that seek to advance AAC’s vision of building a supportive, empowered, and engaged Afghan-American community. \n\n Learn more about our 2019 Planning Team: https://tinyurl.com/y3tzdhlc\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title1_planning_team">Organizing Committee</string>
    <string name="title2_planning_team">2019 Subcommittee</string>


    <string name="title_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="text_faq">
        I REGISTERED FOR A ONE DAY PASS AND/OR JUST FOR MY SESSION, BUT WOULD LIKE TO STAY FOR THE ENTIRE CONFERENCE. HOW CAN I UPGRADE MY REGISTRATION?\n\nPlease visit the Registration Desk located outside of the Crystal Cove Auditorium in the Student Center building. \n\nWHERE DO I REGISTER AND PICK UP MY BADGE\n\nThe registration &amp; badge desk is located outside of the Crystal Cove Auditorium in the Student Center building. The registration desk will open at 9am on Friday, June 21st.\n\nDO I NEED TO BRING A PICTURE ID TO REGISTER?\n\nYes, a picture ID will be required to register and pick-up your badge.\n\nDO I NEED TO WEAR MY BADGE THROUGHOUT THE CONFERENCE?\n\nParticipants are required to wear their badge throughout the conference with no exceptions.\n\nI FORGOT/LOST MY BADGE, CAN I GET IT REPLACED?\n\nThere will be a $25 charge to replace any lost badges with no exceptions. To replace a lost badge, please visit the Registration Desk outside the Crystal Cove Auditorium.\n\nIf you forgot your badge at your hotel, you have the option of going to your hotel to get it or paying the replacement fee, but you are required to return one of your badges to the Registration Resk the following day.\n\nCAN I BRING GUESTS WITH ME TO THE CONFERENCE?\n\nNo, we cannot accommodate any unregistered guests at the Conference. Only participants that have registered to attend will be allowed on Conference premises with their participant name badge.\n\nWHERE IS THE PRAYER AREA LOCATED?\n\nGiven space constraints, the prayer area may shift daily.  Please visit the Registration Desk for exact prayer location or ask a Planning Team Member or Conference Ambassador.\n\nWHAT IS THE CLOSEST PARKING STRUCTURE?\n\nWe recommend parking in the Student Center Parking Structure, which is directly across Pereira Drive from the Student Center. Do not park at the University Towne Center, as they tow cars there. If for some reason the Student Center Parking Structure is full, you may also park in the Social Science Parking Structure. You may purchase a daily permit using credit card or cash.\n\nHOW MUCH IS PARKING?\n\nParking at the above listed structure is $10/day.\n\nWHERE SHOULD UBER/LYFT DROP ME OFF? \n\nPlease type “UCI Student Center &amp; Event Services.” If using Uber, typing that will be sufficient. If using Lyft, you can then select “Student Center.”\n\nI AM FEELING REALLY OVERWHELMED, WHO CAN I REACH OUT TO?\n\nThe AAC Care Team is comprised of mental health professionals available throughout the weekend of the conference. To connect to a member of the Care Team:\n\n1. Send a message to (240) 513-8190‬. Make sure to include your name and a brief message so we connect you with the best person.\n\n2. An available CARE Team member will contact you as soon as possible to coordinate a designated place to meet or set up a phone call.\n\nCAN I BRING FOOD/DRINKS INTO THE CLASSROOMS?\n\nUnfortunately, food and drinks are not permitted in classrooms.\n\nWILL LUGGAGE CHECK BE PROVIDED ON SUNDAY, JUNE 23RD?\n\nUnfortunately, we do not have a designated space to store your luggage. We recommend you check-in your luggage at your hotel bell desk.\n\nWHAT HAPPENS IF I SHOW UP LATE?\n\nWe encourage all participants to arrive on time every day. To respect our speakers, doors will close to all plenary sessions and registered participants that arrive late will be asked to wait outside until the speaker on stage concludes their remarks.\n\nWHERE IS LOST AND FOUND LOCATED?\n\nIf you find a lost item, please return it at the Registration Desk located outside the Crystal Cove Auditorium. If you\’ve lost an item, please visit the registration desk.\n\nWHAT IS THE DRESS CODE?\n\nWe kindly ask participants to dress in business casual attire. However, some participants have changed into Afghan attire for the banquet, and we recommend wearing your AAC shirt on Sunday.\n\nDO I NEED TO CHANGE FOR THE BANQUET?\n\nYou are not required to change for the banquet. In the past, participants have changed into Afghan attire.\n\nCAN I PURCHASE AN AAC T-SHIRT AT THE CONFERENCE?\n\nA limited supply of t-shirts will be available at the conference outside the Crystal Cove Auditorium. Prices as follows: $25 for Short Sleeve T-shirts / $30 for Long Sleeve Shirts\n\nIS THERE A HASHTAG WE SHOULD USE FOR CONFERENCE PICTURES AND POSTS?\n\nOf course there is! Please tag all pictures and posts with #AfgAm19\n\n
    </string>



    <string name="title_donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="donate_text">
        The Afghan-American Conference is made possible by the generous financial support of our donors and sponsors. As a conference intended to bring together Afghan-Americans from all walks of life, it is our intention to ensure that cost does not become an obstacle to participate. \n\nYour support is critical to our future success, and the sustainability of AAC. Donate today to help us continue to build and expand our work for our community.\n\nWe\'re a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization under the Afghan-American Community Organization, therefore your donation is tax-deductible.
    </string>

    <string name="aacare_text">
        What is the CARE Team?\n\nThe AAC CARE Team contributes to the creation of a safe(r) space at the conference by providing additional support for participants during the weekend. The team is comprised of professional therapists along with those who have experience working in mental health or related fields.\n\nUpon request, the CARE Team is available to check in with particpants who may be experiencing difficulty throughout the weekend. This could range from anxiety being around so many people, being triggered by certain topics, or just needing a person to check-in and talk with. They are available to support you in bringing your fullest self at AAC!\n\nHow to Connect with a CARE Team Member:\n\n1. Send a message to (240) 513-8190‬. Make sure to include your name and a brief message so we connect you with the best person.\n\n2. An available CARE Team member will contact you as soon as possible to coordinate a designated place to meet or set up a phone call.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_aacare">
        AACare
    </string>

    <string name="norms_text">
        1. Step up, Step back\n\n• Let your voice be heard but don\'t dominate the conversation\n\n• Don\'t piggyback\n\n2. Be Mindful of Intent vs. Impact\n\n• Assume the best in others\n\n• Challenge the idea, not the individual\n\n3. Affirm one another\n\n• Engage, support, empower\n\n• Encourage, listen, believe\n\n4. Be Present\n\n• One mic, one voice\n\n• No side convos, whispering, or shouting out\n\n5. Be unreasonable\n\n• Find strength in vulnerability\n\n• Step outside your comfort zone &amp; sit in the discomfort\n\n6. Be Flexible\n\n• Try on new views\n\n• Solicit &amp; accept feedback\n\n7. Honor Each Other\n\n• Maintain confidentiality\n\n• Be on time\n\n• Translate to English, always\n\n8. Connect\n\n• Make new friends\n\n• Sit &amp; talk to someone new each session\n\n9. Take Action\n\n• Forward the work of your community\n\n• Be a catalyst\n\nBrave/Safe Space Additions\n\n1. Challenge the idea, not the person\n\n2. One mic, one voice\n\n3. What\'s said here, stays here\n\n4. No video/audio recordings\n\n5. Speak from your own experience
    </string>
    <string name="title_norms">
        Norms
    </string>

    <string name="sponsor_text">
        AAC would not be possible without the support of our generous sponsors and scholarship donors. \n\nTo view a complete list of our sponsors and scholarship donors, visit: https://tinyurl.com/y5cjyj98\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_sponsor">
        Sponsors &amp;\nScholarships
    </string>
    <string name="title_agenda">
        Agenda
    </string>

    <string name="aaconnect_text">
        WHAT IS AACONNECT?\n\nAAConnect is an Afghan-American network that aims to create a platform for members to share academic and professional resources, opportunities, and skills-based trainings/webinars.\n\nWHAT DOES AACONNECT PROVIDE?\n\n• A global membership base of Afghan professionals and students from various backgrounds, industries, and interests\n\n• Access to a network of jobs, fellowships, and professional/academic resources through our email distribution list\n\n• Social-networking and mentorship opportunities through use of our member directory\n\n• Skills-based training events which include podcasts and forums with industry leaders\n\nHOW DO I JOIN AACONNECT?\n\nAll AAC participants and alumni are automatically enrolled in AAConnect, unless they choose to opt out. If you did not attend AAC, please complete the application below and register for a profile on our directory and we will reach out with next steps.\n\nADDITIONAL QUESTIONS?\n\nPlease feel free to email afghanamericanconnect@gmail.com with any additional questions.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_aaconnect">
        AAConnect
    </string>

    <string name="newsletter_text">
        Already looking to stay connected post-AAC? Sign up for the official Afghan-American Conference newsletter here: http://eepurl.com/cw24IT
    </string>
    <string name="title_newsletter">
        Newsletter
    </string>

    <string name="conferenceeval_text">
        Thank you for attending the 2019 Afghan American Conference!\n\nPlease take a few moments to share your thoughts about AAC 2019 at the end of the conference. Your feedback is very valuable to us!\n\nPlease note: The evaluation URL will be made available on the last day of the conference.
    </string>
    <string name="title_conferenceeval">
        Conference Evaluation
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash__screen">AAC</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="credits_text">
        Photography provided by Wayve Media, Khaled Nurhssein, Arash Azzizada, Shab + Coop, Daud Kabiri, Obaid Hofiani.\n\n AAC mobile application developed by Zohib Zalmy and Omar Noorzay.
    </string>
    <string name="title_credits">
        Credits
    </string>

    <string name="donate_button">
        Donate
    </string>

    <string name="title_cohorts">
        Cohorts
    </string>


    <string name="information_text">
UCI WI-FI\n\nNetwork Name: Student Center Visitors\nPassword: anteaters\n\nSOCIAL MEDIA - Please Tag All Pictures #AfgAm19\n\nIG: @afghanamericanconference - https://tinyurl.com/y3zwahbe\nFB: @afghanamericanconference - https://tinyurl.com/y3f6lda5\nTwitter:@afghanamericanc - https://tinyurl.com/yxcc9owg\nSnapchat: @afghanamericanc\nWebsite: afghanamericanconference.org\n\nTHINGS TO DO IN ORANGE COUNTY:\n\nhttps://tinyurl.com/y2uarvt8\n\nREUNIONS\n\nOfficial AAC Reunions (July 13th-21st). Details to be posted on 2019 AACP Facebook Page\n\n
 </string>
    <string name="title_information">
        Information
    </string>

</resources>
